{"cards":[{"mId":"9db863df-f1d8-4f4b-805a-6974b599ae24","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Placebo","mBack":"A drug which has no physical effects, used in pharmaceutical tests to compare the physical effects of taking a real drug from its psychological effects"},{"mId":"ce297697-ecaf-409a-8561-63ec24a0dbbc","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Placebo Effect","mBack":"When someone\u0027s condition improves because they think they are taking medicine"},{"mId":"6e343701-57fd-4df2-80f5-fd9447abb141","mCardType":"text","mFront":"A side effect","mBack":"An extra, usually bad, occurrence caused by taking a drug"},{"mId":"c8152306-41bc-497d-93ce-f07e5a266515","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Proof","mBack":"To show a particular result after a period of time"},{"mId":"2801209d-c6ed-4d1a-bc45-ddbc111b3be1","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Experiment","mBack":"A test done in order to learn something or to find out whether something works or is true"},{"mId":"854b84b7-cb97-4d89-a73c-117ba891f8ee","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Gene","mBack":"A part of the DNA in a cell which contains information in a special pattern received by each animal or plant from its parents, and which controls its physical development, behaviour, etc"},{"mId":"b588a581-2096-4ff2-9fb2-725d362afe30","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Genetic Modification","mBack":"Changing the structure of the genes of a living thing in order to make it healthier or stronger or more useful to humans"},{"mId":"1d73f44e-3a48-4539-bc4a-ee2c0654e7e2","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Genetically Modified Organisms","mBack":"Plants, animals or micro organisms that have changed through genetic engineering"},{"mId":"f60fdc8d-389d-40c4-a26d-14e5e7850ae7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Clone","mBack":"A plant or animal which has the same genes as the original from which it was produced"},{"mId":"494dae2c-5661-4465-a0e0-8dd8e3ea10d4","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Geoengineering","mBack":"The deliberate large-scale intervention in the Earth\u0027s climate system, in order to try and control global warming"},{"mId":"35f59332-f77b-41ca-851a-7348dacab330","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Cyber","mBack":"A prefix for things related to computers, especially the internet"},{"mId":"92c9752e-3df0-4f1d-af19-78b8aa27bb5c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"High-Tech","mBack":"Using the most advanced and developed machines and methods"},{"mId":"7835f530-e9fa-40ef-972b-aeaef367eb0b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Theory","mBack":"A formal statement of the rules on which a subject of study is based or of ideas which are suggested to explain a fact or event or, more generally, an opinion or explanation"}]}